Giocrisrai Godoy

Profile —

I am a curiosity-driven data scientist, having had experience in multiple areas of software development. In this process I have been involved in the development, web scraping, ETL processes, even carrying out an experimental prototype of neural networks to predict time series.

Hard Skills

Programming languages: Python 3, JavaScript, Google Apps Script

Frameworks and Libraries: Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-learn, Seaborn, Matplotlib

Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB

Version Control System: Git, Github **Methodologies:** Agile, SCRUM, kanban

Cloud: Heroku

Others: Trello, Notion, Workspace google, Tableau, Data Studio, Excel

Soft Skills

Collaborative work, Self-learning, Mentoring Team, Communication with clients, Self-discipline, Curiosity

Work Experience

Development Engineer Geogama | Mar 2019 - present

Improvement of processes, in addition to leading the technological area of the organization through the following functions:

- Process automation, Digital transformation, Management of agile methodology, I+D+i, Data science, Artificial intelligence, Development of environmental technology startup

Continuous Improvement Engineer Rheem | Nov 2017 - Mar 2019

Changes in the kaizen philosophy update process and continuous improvement for manufacturing processes:

- Continuous improvement in metalworking manufacturing machinery, Electronic automation, TPM, 5S, Lean Manufacturing

Education

Platzi Master: 2022-2022 Data Scientist | Software Development

UNIR: 2020-2021 Master's degree Artificial Intelligence

MIT: 2019-2020 Diploma in digital transformation

University of Chile 2019-2019 Revalidation of the title of Civil Mechatronics Engineer

UNEXPO: 2008-2013 Mechatronics Engineer

Certifications By Platzi

Languages

Spanish - Native English - B1